How do you feel when you hear these words?
当你听到这些话时，你感觉如何？
Let's go around and introduce ourselves.
让我们轮流自我介绍一下。
Does that make you want a panic, run, or even hide?
这会让你感到恐慌、想逃跑、甚至躲起来吗？
Well, you won't any more after you watch this video.
看完这个视频，你就再也不会了。
Because I'm going to give you a super simple three-step formula
因为我要给你一个超级简单的三步公式
to introduce yourself professionally with ease and confidence
让你轻松自信地进行职业自我介绍
every single time.
每一次都是如此。
Alright, so this formula has three steps.
好的，这个公式有三个步骤。
First, you're going to say something about the present.
首先，你要说一些关于现在的事情。
Then you're going to mention something briefly about the past.
然后简要地提一下过去。
And then you're going to end your introduction with something about the future.
最后用关于未来的内容结束你的自我介绍。
So, present, past, future.
就是现在、过去、未来。
And the idea here is to keep your introduction short and sweet.
关键是要让你的自我介绍简短而美好。
It should be no longer than about 20 seconds.
不应超过大约20秒。
Step one, the present.
第一步，现在。
So, to start your introduction, you're going to say who you are and what you do now.
开始你的自我介绍时，要说你是谁以及你现在做什么。
So, for example, if it's a more formal situation
比如说，如果是比较正式的场合
and you're in a room with people from other companies,
你和来自其他公司的人在一个房间里
you could say something like,
你可以这样说
Hello, everyone.
大家好。
I'm Jennifer Smith.
我是Jennifer Smith。
I'm a software development manager at ABC Company,
我是ABC公司的软件开发经理
where I'm responsible for the building of new systems
负责构建新系统
and prevention of issues.
和问题预防。
If it's a more informal situation,
如果是比较非正式的场合
stay, you're just starting a new job
比如你刚开始一份新工作
and you're introducing yourself to your new co-workers.
你在向新同事介绍自己。
You could say something like,
你可以这样说
Hi, all.
嗨，大家好。
I'm Joe.
我是Joe。
I'm part of the North America Marketing team,
我是北美市场团队的成员
and I'll be looking after generation of new leads.
负责开发新潜在客户。
Now, here, just mention your primary responsibility,
在这里，只提你的主要职责
not every single task that you do in your job.
而不是你工作中的每一项任务。
And especially if you're working for an American company,
尤其是如果你在一家美国公司工作
don't mention any personal details,
不要提及任何个人信息
like how old you are,
比如你的年龄
whether you're married or single,
你结婚了还是单身
your hobbies just keep it to the professional side.
你的爱好，只局限于职业方面。
Quick question before we move on.
在继续之前，快速提问。
Do you have to speak English in your current job right now?
你目前的工作中需要说英语吗？
Tell me in the comments, either yes or no.
在评论中告诉我，是或不是。
Alright, moving on to step two of the past.
好的，现在进入第二步，过去。
So now is the time where you're going to want to mention something brief
现在是时候简要提一下
and relevant about your background.
关于你背景中相关的事情。
Something that's going to help people get to know you just a little bit more
一些能帮助人们多了解你一点的事情
and also establishes your credibility.
同时也能建立你的可信度。
So think about some things that are relevant to the people you're talking to.
想想那些与你的谈话对象相关的事情。
Things like past projects, companies you've worked for other achievements
比如过去的项目、你工作过的公司、其他成就
and just pick one of those things to highlight.
从中选一个来突出说明。
So one example might be,
一个例子可能是
my background is in computer science.
我的背景是计算机科学。
Before taking on this role,
在担任这个职位之前
I work with big data together insights for our clients
我利用大数据为客户整合洞察
and the financial services industry.
在金融服务行业。
Or, I've been with the company for two years now.
或者，我在这家公司已经工作两年了。
Most recently, I was part of the team who worked on campaign ABC,
最近，我参与了ABC项目的团队
which brought us client X.
为我们带来了客户X。
So the key thing here is to keep it brief and irrelevant.
这里的关键是保持简短和相关。
Now is not the time to be telling your whole life story
现在不是讲述你整个人生故事的时候
or giving a summary of your whole CD and resume or your career history.
也不是概括你整份简历或职业经历的时候。
And step three, the future.
第三步，未来。
Here you want to end your introduction on a positive note
在这里，你要以积极的语气结束你的自我介绍
and show some enthusiasm for the topic at hand.
并对当前话题表现出一些热情。
Communicate some good energy and show the people in the room
传达一些正能量，让房间里的人知道
that you're happy to be there and you're happy to be involved.
你很高兴能来到这里并参与其中。
And it can be simple.
这可以很简单。
For example, you could just say,
比如，你可以直接说
it's a pleasure to be here with you all today.
今天很高兴能和大家在一起。
I'm looking very forward to working with you.
我非常期待与你们共事。
Or more informally,
或者更随意一些
I'm excited to be part of this project.
我很兴奋能参与这个项目。
I think it'll be a great opportunity for all of us.
我认为这对我们所有人来说都是一个很好的机会。
Alright, now if you put all three of these steps together,
好的，现在如果你把这三步结合起来
here's an example of how a full introduction might sound.
这是一个完整自我介绍可能听起来的样子。
Hi, everyone.
大家好。
I'm Maria Shearan.
我是Maria Shearan。
I'm a marketing manager at ABC Company,
我是ABC公司的市场经理
where I'm responsible for lead generation campaigns for North America.
负责北美的潜在客户开发活动。
I've been with a company for five years now.
我在这家公司已经五年了。
Prior to that, I managed the social media efforts
在此之前，我管理了社交媒体工作
for company XYZ.
为XYZ公司。
It's a pleasure to be here today
今天很高兴来到这里
and I'm really looking forward to working with you all in this project.
我真的很期待与大家一起参与这个项目。
So just remember, present past future.
所以只要记住，现在、过去、未来。
Pretty easy, right?
很简单，对吧？
But don't stop there.
但不要止步于此。
Keep practicing your English-speaking skills
继续练习你的英语口语技能
that you get more and more comfortable speaking
让你越来越自如地使用英语
and English in these kinds of work situations.
在这种工作场合中。
And you can do that with this video right here.
你可以通过这里的这个视频来做到。
Thank you so much for watching and I'll see you there next.
非常感谢收看，我们下次再见。